my check my check one two all right guys in this video what I want to do is I
我检查了一下两个好人 在这个视频中我想做的 是我
want to show you guys how to make a word counter and what this is basically going
想告诉你们如何说一句话 反击， 这基本上是 什么
to do is it's going to go through a web page and you can actually use it even if you have like a text file or I don't
要做的是它将 通过网络 页面 实际上 ， 你 可以使用它 ， 即使 你喜欢文本文件，或者我没有
know any document but I'm just going to show you guys how to crawl a web page
知道任何文件，但我只是去 告诉你们如何抓取一个网页
get all the words on there and what it's going to do is it's going to show you
得到那里的所有文字及其内容 要做的是它会 告诉你
guys how frequently each word is used now search engines actually do this a
伙计们每个单词的使用频率 现在搜索引擎 实际上是这样做的
lot in arm maybe you have an ad network that you're building and you want to
也许你有一个广告网络 你正在建设你 想要的
display ads that are relevant to the content on the web pages so not only is
显示广告是相关 的 网页上的内容 不仅如此
this really interesting but it's useful in a lot of situations as well so what
这真的很有趣， 但它很有用 在很多 情况 以及 等什么
we're going to be doing is we're going to import requests and of course we need this for whenever we connect to URL and
我们将做 的是我们要去 导入请求，当然我们需要 这对于每当 我们连线至URL和
get information from it pretty much to download information from a web page
从它那里得到的信息相当多的 从网页下载信息
we're going to request that information not just the mandate you know got to be
我们将 请求信息 不只是任务 ，你知道该杀
nice about it and the next thing we're going to do is import beautifulsoup
对它很好， 接下来 就是我们 要做的是进口 beautifulsoup
remember whenever you want to scrape or um pick out certain pieces of the web
记得每当你想刮或 嗯挑出 网络的某些部分
page and I'll show you guys what I'm talking about right here so the reason
页面 ，我会告诉你们我的意思 谈到这里 如此的原因
that we just don't want to crawl every single word on this web page is because
我们只是 不想抓狂 这个网页上的 单个词 是 因为
some of the words like likes comments likes comments they appear all the time
一些喜欢评论的词 喜欢的意见，他们出现在所有的时间
but they aren't really relevant on this web page the only relevant words that
但他们不会 在这个 真正 相关的 网页唯一相关的单词
I'm looking for is pretty much these links right here so we can ignore all
我正在寻找的就是 这些 链接就在这里， 所以我们可以忽略所有
the words like posted September all the crap we don't need and beautiful soups
9月所发布的所有内容 垃圾，我们不需要和美丽的汤
going to allow us to do that and the last thing we need is import operator and that's arm whenever we make the
允许我们 这样 做 和 我们需要的最后一件事是进口运营商 每当我们制作时 ，那都是我的手臂
final word count we're going to have a dictionary we're going to have the words
最后的字数我们将有一个 字典我们要说的话
like I don't know programmer status and those are going to be the keys and the
就像我不知道程序员的状态和 那些将是关键和
values are going to be how many times they occurred so it's going to say something like arm like programming 18
价值 将 是多少 倍 它们发生了，所以它会说 像 手臂一样的东西18
times by two times something like that so now let's go ahead and get started so
两次 这样的事情 所以现在让我们开始吧等等
the first thing we need to do is obviously make a function and I'm
我们需要做的第一 件事 显然是一个功能，我
going to be breaking up this program into three functions the first function
打算 破解这个计划 第一个功能 分为 三个功能
is just going to create a list of every single word on here so that's what I'm
只是要创建 一个列表 单词就在这里 ，这就是我的意思
doing first and I'll explain you guys the other functions when we get to them
先做，我会解释你们 当我们到达他们时，其他功能
but oh my oh my I put in PI but since this is our starting point what I want
但哦，我的哦，我 把它放在PI但是从那以后 这是 我想要的 出发点
to do is just name it start why the heck not and pass it in a URL so actually
要做的只是命名它开始 为什么哎呀 实际上并没有在URL中传递它
what I can do actually I'll call that later don't want
我可以做什么 实际上我会打电话给后来 不想要的
to really worry about it now all right so the first thing we need to do is we
真的很担心它现在 好了 所以我们需要做的第一件事就是我们
need to create a blank list so word list and then just set this equal to blank
需要 创建一个空白的列表 ，以便单词列表 然后将其设置为空白
list and eventually what we're going to be doing is arm getting all the source
列出并最终我们要去做什么 做的是 手臂获得 所有来源
code from the website and picking out word by word and throwing it in that
来自 网站的代码和 挑选 一字一句地扔在那里
list so to connect the web page of course requests get and get pretty much means all right what do you want to get
列出这样连接的网页 课程要求得到并得到 相当多 意味着你想得到什么
information from well whatever URL we pass in which is essentially going to be
来自我们的任何URL的信息 通过其本质上将是
this URL and again like I said you can pretty much do this for any web page but
这个网址再次像我说的那样 几乎对任何网页都这样做但是
I just don't want to like go to Craigslist or something or else I'm
我只是不想喜欢去 Craigslist 或者别的 什么 我也是
going to get the email bag of Bucky you can't do that to our web page and then
要得到 巴基 您 的电子邮件 袋 不能那样做到我们的网页 然后
I'm going to sue me so I'll just do it to my own for now if you guys want to
我要起诉 我，所以 我就做 如果你们想要，我现在就自己
crawl my web page that's fine I give you permission just don't like abuse it or
抓住我的网页，我给你的很好 许可只是不喜欢滥用它或
anything all right so what this is going to do is it's going to connect to that
什么都 没事，所以 这是怎么回事 要做的就是 连接到那个
URL or that web page and this means pretty much just use it as plain text don't like I'll pull it as any weird
URL或该网页 ，这 意味着 几乎 只是用它作为纯文本 不喜欢我会把它拉得像任何奇怪的
encrypted binary data or anything like that so now that we have pretty much all
加密的二进制数据或类似的东西 那 所以现在我们有几乎所有
the source code from the web page what we're looking at is pretty much this all
来自网页的源代码是 什么 我们正在关注的是这一切
of that crap now of course whenever we use beautifulsoup
废话 现在 当然，每当我们 使用beautifulsoup
we need to convert that to a soup object so take that source code that you just
我们需要将其转换为汤对象 所以拿那个你刚才的源代码吧
grabbed and throw in here and now your soup
抓住并扔进这里，现在你的 汤
object is something that you can actually work with so what I want to do
对象是你可以做到的 实际上我正在做我想做的事情
is I would want to do this and come on capslock so right now we're looking at
我想要 做到这一点并加油 所以现在我们正在关注
all this crap and of course we don't just want to crawl all this or else
所有这些废话 当然 我们没有 只是想 抓住 这 一切 或其他
we're going to get weird keywords like div class you know IMG we don't care
我们会得到一些奇怪的关键词 div class你知道IMG 我们不在乎
about that what we care about is only the text and these links right here so
关于 我们关心的只是 文本和这些链接就 在这里
let's go ahead and inspect this and see what property is unique to these links and if I scroll up you guys are going to
让我们继续 检查并查看 什么属性是这些 链接 所特有的 如果我滚动你们要
see so of course whenever I highlight this this is the link that we're looking for so it says okay this href changes so
当我突出强调时，当然可以看到 这是我们正在 寻找 的链接 因为 它说好了这个href改变了
we can't really use that the class however if we edit this all of these
我们不能真正使用那个班级 但是，如果我们编辑所有这些
links or all the important content has a class of index single listing titles so
链接或所有重要内容都有 索引单一列表标题如此
let's go ahead and grab that I just cut it or you can copy it whatever and what
让我们继续前进，抓住我刚切 它或你可以复制 它什么和什么
I want to do is write this for post text this is just a variable that because
我想做的是写这篇文章 这只是一个变量，因为
it's a text from each post and soup find all now find all remember you says okay
这是每个帖子 和汤找到的文本 所有现在发现都记得你说好的
we're going to go through all that source code what are you looking for
我们要经过 所有 源代码你在找什么？
well first of all it was a link so it was a and the next thing it needs is it
首先，它是一个链接所以它 是一个，它需要的下一件事是它
pretty much says okay now I'm going to look at all the links now what property do you want me to look for well only
几乎说好 了我现在要去 看看现在所有的链接属性 你想让我只找好
grab the links with the class of index single listing titles so now essentially
抓住索引类的链接 现在基本上是单个列表标题
what we have is all of these links right here however we have one problem what we
我们拥有的是所有这些链接 然而 在这里 ，我们有 一个问题， 就是我们
have is actually the entire like all of it so we have href we have this part we have this part and we have the content
有实际上是像所有的整 它所以我们有href我们有这个部分我们 有这个部分 ，我们 有内容
that we need now if we only want to pull out this good content you know kind of
如果我们只想拉，我们现在需要 你知道这个好的内容
like stealing the cream from the milk we need to do this so the
喜欢偷奶油 从牛奶我们需要做到这一点， 所以
content which is basically what we're looking for is equal to post text string
内容基本上就是我们的内容 寻找等于发布文本字符串
so that's going to do is it's going to go through your entire source code pull
所以这将做的是它会 完成整个源代码拉
out all of the important links and treat them as post text now post text string
了解所有重要的链接和对待 它们作为帖子文本现在发布 文本字符串
pretty much means only get the text that's inside here don't even worry
几乎意味着只得到文本 里面的内容甚至 不用担心
about this HTML crap so this is pretty much how you remove HTML from some of
关于这个HTML垃圾，所以这很漂亮 多，你是如何 从 一些 删除HTML
them probably could have just said that but who cares so now we have all the
他们也许可以刚才说 ， 但是现在我们关心所有人
good stuff however we have one more problem and I
好东西 但是，我们有更多的一个 问题 ，我
know this is kind of a lot of information but it's important so right
知道这是怎样的一个很大的 信息，但它是如此正确
now we have a bunch of sentences and we don't want the entire sentences for each
现在我们有一堆 句子和 我们 不想要每个 句子的整个句子
one we just want the words so we we don't want arm all of this in a variable
一个我们 只想要的话， 所以我们 不希望 所有 这些都在变量中
we want to break it up into Ben and then stuck here all day and those are
我们 想把 它分解成Ben然后 整天都在这里， 而且那些都是
individual words because that's that's what this program does so in order to do
单词，因为那就是那个 这是什么程序 ， 为了 做到 这样做
that we need one more variable and I'll just name it words it's set to equal to
我们需要一个变量 ，我会 只需将其 设置为等于的 单词
content dot lower split actually this one is lower to now the reason so well
内容点低分实际上这个 一个是低到现在这么好的原因
I'll explain what this does so content is basically the entire sentence so what
我会解释这是什么内容 基本上整个句子都是 如此
we want to do first is the lower case everything in that sentence and that's
我们想先做的是小写 那句话 中的一切都是如此
just because some people start a sentence with like I and some people
只是因为有些 人开始了 像我和一些人一样的句子
aren't using proper grammar or I don't know what's something in here like maybe
没有使用正确的语法，或者我没有 知道 这里有什么东西可能
they're talking about this guy Richard Feynman I've no idea who that is
他们在谈论这个人理查德 费曼我不知道 那是谁
but not everyone capitalizes things in the exact same way so we want to do just
但不是每个人都把事情都搞好了 完全相同的方式， 所以 我们想做的只是
to make sure everything is consistent and we don't get any duplicate results
确保一切都是一致的 我们没有得到任何重复的结果
it's just lower case everything and split basically splits up your string
它只是小写的一切和 split基本上会拆分你的字符串
based on spaces so it basically takes a sentence and splits it up into words so
基于空间所以它 基本上需要 一个 句子，将其分解 成的话 让
that's why I have each word now in this variable so now we can
这就是我拥有的原因 现在我们可以 在这个变量 中使用
look through it for each word in words what do I want to do well now that we have the individual words we can just
通过 它 寻找在字，每个字 我们现在想做什么呢？ 有我们可以说的单词
add it to our main word list so word list and of course whenever you want to
将它添加到我们的主要单词列表，所以单词 列表 ，当然还有你想要的
add something use append and of course what are we appending or what are we
添加一些使用附加物，当然 我们追加什么或者我们是什么
adding to the list we're adding each word so now actually I'll print this out
添加 到 列表中我们正在添加每个 所以现在实际上 我会把它打印 出来
real quick print each word all right so now if I run this check it out and
真正快速打印每个单词都可以 所以现在，如果我运行这个检查出来
nothing happens because I actually need to call this at some point in time so
没有任何反应，因为我真的需要 在某个 时间 点 这样 称呼它
that's the function that I want to call and I want to call for this URL all
这就是我想要调用的功能 我想打电话给这个URL
right so now give me some space and run this check it out what we did is we
对，所以现在给我一些空间 并运行 这检查出我们做的是我们
connect it to that website and we got the source code we broke it up in the
将它连接到该网站 ，我们得到了 源代码我们把它分解了
sentences or the good stuff and then we broke those sentences up into words and
句子或好东西，然后我们 将这些句子分成了单词和
we now have a list of all of the words on the website however if we look
我们现在有一个 所有单词 的列表 如果我们看的话 ，在网站上
closely at this we have a couple problems first of all we have symbols
我们 有一 对夫妇 问题首先我们有符号
that we don't need like this okay has three dots after it this thing this
我们不需要像这样没关系 这个东西之后有三个点
isn't even word that's just a smiley face but I mean I followed our
甚至不是那个只是笑脸的词 面对但我的意思是我跟着我们
instructions that's what we told it to do and there's some other stuff here that's weird like debatable has a some
说明就是我们告诉它的 这里有其他一些东西 像辩论那样奇怪有一些
symbols after it so we need to clean that up so what we're going to be doing
之后的符号所以我们需要清理 ， 最多 我们要等什么 是做
is we're going to be cleaning up all this stuff in the next tutorial and I'm
我们将要清理所有 这个东西在下一个教程中，我
going to show you guys how to make a proper nicely perfectly working word
要告诉你们 如何制作 一个 适当的完美工作词
counter so that's what we have to look forward to I'll see you then
这是我们必须要看的东西 转发到 我会看到你再